A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Human Rights and Governance Program, Program Director, Office Files of Shepard Forman FA717
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Trip Files, 1981-1990; V
  - Cairo/Israel, 1989 October 22 - 31 (Box 16 (SK #38675), Folder 6)
  - AAA Meeting, 1989 November 11 - 19 (Box 16 (SK #38675), Folder 7)
  - Houston, TX: Nestor Rodriguez, 1989 October 11-12 (Box 16 (SK #38675), Folder 8)
  - Vienna, 1990 January (Box 16 (SK #38675), Folder 9)
  - Budapest, Hungary, 1990 January (Box 16 (SK #38675), Folder 10)
  - Latin America, 1990 January (Box 16 (SK #38675), Folder 11)
  - Budapest, Hungary, 1990 February (Box 16 (SK #38675), Folder 12)
  - Washington, D.C., 1990 February (Box 16 (SK #38675), Folder 13)
  - Puerto Rico, 1990 February 28 - March 2 (Box 16 (SK #38675), Folder 14)
  - Boston: Council on Foundations, 1990 April 2 (Box 16 (SK #38675), Folder 15)
  - Boston: Barone Center, 1990 May 3 - 4 (Box 16 (SK #38675), Folder 16)
  - Washington, D.C., 1990 May 16 (Box 16 (SK #38675), Folder 17)
  - Soviet Union: Wingspread (Cancelled), 1990 May 22 (Box 16 (SK #38675), Folder 18)
  - Hungary, 1990 June 18 - 20 (Box 16 (SK #38675), Folder 19)
  - Vienna: Vienna Institute for Human Sciences, 1990 June 28 - July 1 (Box 16 (SK #38675), Folder 20)
  - Brazil, 1990 July (Box 16 (SK #38675), Folder 21)
  - Prague, Czechoslovakia, 1990 September 7 - 17 (Box 16 (SK #38675), Folder 22)
- Appendix A: Reports
  Arrangement
  The following reports were transferred to the Ford Foundation Archives Reports Collection. The number at the left is the assigned accession number. The list is alphabetical by author.
  - Carpenter, Margaret and Elizabeth Midgley. Evaluation of the National Immigration, Refugee and Citizenship Program (Report 13825)
  - Castoreno, Cathrine. U.S. Hispanics at Mid-Decade (Report 13831)
  - Caughman, Susan. Women at Work in Mali: the Case of the Markala Cooperative (Report 7016)
  - Espinoza, Wilma. A Review of National Hispanic Women's Organizations (Report 13675)
  - Findley, Dru. The Impact of Recent Events in China on International Professional and Academic Exchanges and Related Development Activities (Report 13832)
  - Forman, Shepard and Diana Morris. Rapporteur Notes on the Human Rights and Social Justice Meeting in Geneva (Report 13833)
  - Harrington, Christine B. An Overview of the Dispute Resolution Field (Report 13827)
  - Lacy Jr., Madison, D. Fostering Diversity in Public Television (Report 13824)
  - Neblett, Richard and Walter Plotch. Black Organizations and Fund-raising: A Review (Report 13828)
  - Rapoprt, Rhona. Advancement of Blacks and Women in South Africa (Report 13671)
  - Subak, Susan. A Survey of U. S. Environmental Organizations' Activities in Sustainable Development (Report 13826)
  - Walker, Lynn and Mora McLean. Voter Registration and Education Projects: A Profile of Ford Foundation Grantees (Report 13830)
  - Yu, Peter M. The American Electoral System: Issues and Considerations (Report 13829)